<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tattoo Zone</string>
    <string name="subscribe_inst">Try 3-day free trial, then subscribe  to $319.99/ 3 Months. Go pro to get all updates and tattoo tricks from Masterminds. There will be a charge to your account 3 days after subscription. Go to Google play settings to stop auto-renewal. /n CLICK SUBSCRIBE TO CONTINUE</string>

    <string name="tattoo_1_desc">Amazing Shree Calligraphy Tattoo By Devendra Palav at Aliens Tattoo India. If you wish to get this tattoo visit our website www.alienstattoo.com</string>
    <string name="tattoo_2_desc">Watercolor Mandala Tattoo by Allan Gois And Devendra Palav at Aliens Tattoo India. If you wish to get this tattoo visit our website</string>
    <string name="tattoo_3_desc">"We are all a little damaged, Bee. Some of us more than others.”― T.M. Frazier, The Dark Light of Day </string>
    <string name="tattoo_4_desc">“My body is my journal, and my tattoos are my story.”― Johnny Depp </string>
    <string name="tattoo_5_desc">“Show me a man with a tattoo and I will show you a man with an interesting past.” ― Jack London </string>
    <string name="tattoo_6_desc">“Wear your heart on your skin in this life.”― Sylvia Plath </string>
    <string name="tattoo_7_desc">“Books are to me as homemade tattoos are to an inmate. Can not get enough of them.”― Laurie Notaro, I Love Everybody </string>
    <string name="tattoo_8_desc">“I am a canvas of my experiences, my story is etched in lines and shading, and you can read it on my arms, my legs, my shoulders, and my stomach.”― Kat Von D </string>
    <string name="tattoo_9_desc">“We are all a little damaged, Bee. Some of us more than others.”― T.M. Frazier, The Dark Light of Day </string>
    <string name="tattoo_10_desc">“She had a flower tattoo on her wrist; "What does that mean?" he asked her. "Absolutely nothing," she said, "it's just a flower.”― C. JoyBell C. </string>
    <string name="tattoo_11_desc">“Our bodies were printed as blank pages to be filled with the ink of our hearts”― Michael Biondi </string>
    <string name="tattoo_12_desc">“The cafe was called Tattoos. The fella who owned it did not have any tattoos... but we never saw his wife.” ― Karl Pilkington </string>
    <string name="tattoo_13_desc">“They keep track of time. Sometimes things happen and you feel that you need to mark them down.”― Scott OConnor, Untouchable </string>
    <string name="tattoo_14_desc">“Seriously, what is it about men in jeans and bare feet which is so totally hot?”― Samantha Towle </string>
    <string name="tattoo_15_desc">“This would go a lot easier if you would stop screaming in pain,  Zoe told the muscular man lying beneath her.” ― Jaime Rush </string>
    <string name="tattoo_16_desc">“I don’t have any myself,” Mia said, her voice slow and deliberate. “But I’ve always found tattoos sexy.”― Katherine McIntyre, Confined Desires </string>
    <string name="tattoo_17_desc">"That will become inaccurate at some point, " Omar pointed out.” ― Domashita Romero, Complicated Creation </string>

</resources>
